// build array of question objects

//q: string
//a1:
//a2:
//a3:
//a4:
//CA:

var question1 = {
    question: "To out put a message to the web console you would use what method? " ,
    a1:"print.out()",
    a2:"console.log()",
    a3:"output()",
    a4:"log.out()",
    correctAnswer: "a2"
};


var question2 = {
    question: "Which of these is not a data type in javaScript? " ,
    a1:"boolean",
    a2:"number",
    a3:"string",
    a4:"pointer",
    correctAnswer: "a4"
};

var question3 = {
    question: "Which of these correctly builds an empty array in javaScript?" ,
    a1:"newArray=()",
    a2:"newArray={}",
    a3:"newArray=<>",
    a4:"newArray=[]",
    correctAnswer: "a4"
};

var question4 = {
    question: "What does the '%' do in JavaScript?" ,
    a1:"Multiply",
    a2:"Returns remainder",
    a3:"Creates a new object",
    a4:"Points to the head",
    correctAnswer: "a2"
};

var question5 = {
    question: "What is the proper load order for css.reset and css.style?" ,
    a1:"style first",
    a2:"Order doesn't matter",
    a3:"Reset first",
    a4:"Reset doesn't get linked",
    correctAnswer: "a3"
};

var question6 = {
    question: "WHich of the following is NOT a functionality available to JavaScript?" ,
    a1:"Multi-threading",
    a2:"Object-oriented programming",
    a3:"Storing data in variables",
    a4:"Storing objects in arrays",
    correctAnswer: "a1"
};

var question7 = {
    question: "Which is the proper syntax for adding a list item to HTML?" ,
    a1:"<list>",
    a2:"<li>",
    a3:"list-item",
    a4:"<list-item>",
    correctAnswer: "a2"
};

var question8 = {
    question: "Which of these would be largest on the screen (assuming no styling)?" ,
    a1:"<h1>",
    a2:"<h2>",
    a3:"<h3>",
    a4:"<h4>",
    correctAnswer: "a1"
};

var question9 = {
    question: "Which of these correctly demonstrates proper variable naming conventions in JavaScript?" ,
    a1:"newArray",
    a2:"newarray",
    a3:"Newarray",
    a4:"nEwArrAy",
    correctAnswer: "a1"
};

var question10 = {
    question: "Which of these demonstrates proper syntax for a 'for' loop?" ,
    a1:"for{let i= 1 , i <= 100; i++}{//some code here//}",
    a2:"for (let i = 1; i <= 100; i++){//some code here//}",
    a3:"for (let i = 1, i <= 100, i++){//some code here//}",
    a4:"for (let i = 1; i <= 100; i++)(//some code here//)",
    correctAnswer: "a2"
};
var questions = [question1, question2, question3, question4, question5, question6];
